Pretty Fly
Give it to me baby, uh-huh, uh-huh
And all the girlies say I'm pretty fly for a white guy
Uno, dos, tres, cuatro, cinco, cinco, seis
You know it's kind of hard just to get along today
Our subject isn't cool, but he thinks it anyway
He may not have a clue and he may not have style
But everything he lacks, well, he makes up in denial
So, do the ditty, play it straight
You know he really doesn't get it anyway
Got to play the field, keep it real
For you, no way, for you, no way
So if you don't rate, just overcompensate
At least you know you can always go on Ricki Lake
The world needs wannabes
Hey, hey, do that brand new thing
Give it to me baby, uh-huh, uh-huh
And all the girlies say I'm pretty fly for a white guy
He needs some cool tunes, not just any will suffice
But they didn't have Ice Cube so he bought Vanilla Ice
Now cruising in his Pinto, he sees homies as he pass
But if he looks twice, they're gonna kick his lily ass
So, do the ditty, play it straight
You know he really doesn't get it anyway
Got to play the field, keep it real
For you, no way, for you, no way
So if you don't rate, just overcompensate
At least you know you can always go on Ricki Lake
The world needs wannabes
Hey, hey, do that brand new thing
Now he's getting a tattoo, yeah, he's getting ink done
He asked for a 13, but they drew a 31
Friends say he's trying too hard and he's not quite hip
But in his own mind, he's the, he's the dopest trip
Give it to me baby, uh-huh, uh-huh
Uno, dos, tres, cuatro, cinco, cinco, seis
So, do the ditty, play it straight
You know he really doesn't get it anyway
Got to play the field, keep it real
For you, no way, for you, no way
So if you don't rate, just overcompensate
At least you know you can always go on Ricki Lake
The world needs wannabes
The world loves wannabes
Let's get another wannabe
Hey, hey, do that brand new thing